{
    "subject": "resource/Regent_University",
    "predicate": "property/colors",
    "object": "Blue, Green",
    "human_readable": "The colors of Regent University are Blue and Green.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8651935458183289,
            "question": "What are the colors of Regent University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7108621001243591,
            "question": "List the two main colors associated with Regent University."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6589462161064148,
            "question": "Are there any other universities with similar color schemes to Regent University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6270205974578857,
            "question": "Could the colors of Regent University be symbolic of something specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5846294164657593,
            "question": "What colors are prominently displayed on Regent University's logo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5767829418182373,
            "question": "What might be the historical significance behind choosing these colors for Regent University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5153777003288269,
            "question": "Which color is NOT part of Regent University's official color scheme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5011277198791504,
            "question": "Do you think the colors of Regent University evoke a particular feeling or message?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49894845485687256,
            "question": "If Regent University held a sporting event, what colors would their team wear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4699879288673401,
            "question": "How might the colors of Regent University be used in their marketing materials?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The colors of Regent University are Blue and Green.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5497_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If Regent University held a sporting event, what colors would their team wear?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5497_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you think the colors of Regent University evoke a particular feeling or message?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5497_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which color is NOT part of Regent University's official color scheme?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5497_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5497_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. In fact, it states that Regent's colors are indeed \"Regent's colors\u2014blue and green\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states, \"In a tradition that Regent graduates anticipate: a flurry of confetti in Regent\u2019s colors\u2014blue and green\u2014cascaded over the graduates,\" which supports the statement that the colors of Regent University are Blue and Green."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}